Curriculum vitae

Mohammad Amir Jamali

mohammadamirjamali2020@gmail.com

Mashhad, Iran 🔾

21 September, 1991 mm

GitHub 🕥

LinkedIn in

Blog ...

I hold a Master's degree in Information Technology Management - E-Commerce, and I have established a strong foundation in various programming languages. In addition to my programming skills, I have developed a keen interest in the fields of Machine Learning and Quantum Computing (QML). Furthermore, I possess a wealth of experience in successfully launching and overseeing startup ventures.

EDUCATION

Master's in Information Technology E-Commerce

Islamic Azad University, Birjand branch 09/2017 - 11/2019

Bachelor's in Industrial Engineering

Payam Noor University, Birjand branch 11/2009 - 02/2014

RESEARCH

- An introduction to Quantum Computing; Advantages and challenges (6th National Conference on Distributed Computing and Big Data Processing) 2021
- Comparison of the local generalization error model (LG Trader) with the exponential moving average (EMA) in selecting stocks with the highest return rate 2019 (Fourth National Conference on Applied Research in Electrical Engineering, Mechanics, Computer and Information Technology.)
- Predicting Bitcoin price with Bayesian Neural Network by using COT weekly report(Master's thesis) 2019

SELECTED HONORS AND AWARDS

- Involved in finalists of UCL Hatchery Social Enterprise Award with Enviroble.Ltd (Santander Awards 2022)
- Ranked as the second-highest GPA among MSc students in the Computer Science faculty, with a GPA of 3.88/4.

EXPERTISE

- Machine Learning (Neural Networks and other Machine Learning techniques)
- Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP 2008)
- Programming Languages:
 - > **JS**: JavaScript, Node, React, AJAX, NextJs, Express, Redux, Socket.io (MERN Stack)
 - PHP: WordPress Theme and Plugins Customization (Woocommerce, Stripe Connect, WC Vendor, Redis, Elastic Search, Creating Gutenberg Blocks, Elementor, WP CLI...),
 - > Python: Web scraping (Scrapy, Selenium), Django (DRF, Redis, Celery, PyTest, Locust, Silk, Postgrsql), Cirq(Quantum Computing), TensorFlow
 - ➤ **MQL** (c++): Expert Advisor programing

WORK EXPERIENCE

СТО

Enviroble.com

University College London BaseKX

03/2021 - 11/2022

London-UK

Founder

cikit.ir

01/2020 - 02/2021

Mashhad-Iran

Founder

Class724.ir

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

05/2017 - 11/2019

Birjand-Iran

Partner

Daneshjooyar.com

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

10/2015 - 01/2017

Birjand-Iran

FAMILIAR WITH

AWS DevOps

System Design

Microservice Architecture

Jenkins

Git / GitLab

Agile Methodologies

RabbitMQ

Github Actions

Docker

kubernetes

Travis-CI Postgrsql

MongoDB

Cassandra

Terraform

SKILLS

Collaborative Flexibility

Studious

Positive Engagement

Initiative Driven

INTERESTS

Music

Workout

Travel

Environmental Activities

Technology

LANGUAGES

English Professional Arabic Native

Farsi Native